

Ostap Klysa Frontend Developer (Junior)

About me

I am Ostap Klysa, web developer from Porto, Portugal. I'm using HTML, CSS/SASS, JS and some frameworks to create websites. Experience of creation websites without design. Work experience with Backend Framework (October CMS). Understanding splicing frontend from backend. Or creation frontend for ready backend (backoffice). I like to try something new!

Currently improving my English and study JavaScript and some Frameworks (Vue Js, React Js).

Age 24

Number +351 937373213

Email ostapklysa@gmail.com

Hobbies

Coding some code for me
Listen to music when coding
Driving and speak about cars

My Skills

Contacts

HTML 9.5 / 10

Css/Sass 9 / 10

JS 5 / 10

Bootstrap 3/4/5 8/10

TailwindCss

October CMS

(Creating simple sites with backoffice 'Blog', 'Product portfolio').

Work experience with Razor Pages in ASP.NET Core. (Creation of the visual part for exist Razor Pages Backend in Visual Studio).

Fast adaptation to a new project or an existing one.

Understanding splicing frontend from backend (CMS Frameworks, excluding Wordpress).

Work experience

Freelance (12.2019 - present time).

Responsive

Junta Digital Production (03.2017 - 11.2019)

- Responsive
- Css/Sass/Scss
- Bootstrap
- JavaScript/Jquery
- October CMS
- In 2018 responsible for Front-End (project creation, project structure, some project planning, time estimate).

Basepoint (internship) (10.2016 - 12.2016).

- Responsive
- Css
- JavaScript

Engetec (internship) (5.2014 - 07.2014).

- Diagnostic (Desktops & Laptops)
- Repairs Software e Hardware

Knowledge

Git

Terminal

Linux (terminal navigate and use as a workspace).

Slack

Adobe XD

Figma

Avocode

Invision Studio

Trello (Project tracking).

JIRA (Sourcetree App, Issue & Project tracking).

Education

Curso web developer CESAE (06.2016 - 12.2016).

- HTM
- CSS
- JavaScript

Curso web developer CESAE (06.2016 - 12.2016).

• Técnico de Gestão Informatica.

My works (most popular)



















